<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project name="Execution Analysis" basedir=".">

	<property name="dvt.activity.name" value="RTOS Analyzer/${ant.project.name}"/>
	<property name="dvt.activity.description" value="RTOS Context Switch events are collected from target and displayed in the Execution Graph.&#10;In a multi-core system, the Concurrency Analysis Feature can be selected to analyze parallel execution. "/>
	<property name="dvt.activity.icon" value="platform:/plugin/com.ti.dvt.ui/icons/views/discrete.gif"/>

	<property name="uc_name" value="Execution" />
	<dvt.import file="../../scripts/SystemAnalyzer.js"/>

	<dvt.property>
		version=1.0.0
		dvt.activity.priority = 130

		<!-- Data Provider and AF information-->
		uiaMode=Live
		dataproviders=UIA
		UIA.name=UIA Log Viewer
		UIA.analyzer=Execution Graph,Concurrency:false,Printf Logs:false,CPU Load:false,Task Load:false,Task Profiler:false,Duration:false,Count Analysis:false,Context Aware Profile:false

		ExecutionGraph.Tip=Select this feature to see Execution Graph showing timeline of Tasks, SWIs and HWIs, Semaphore, RTOS events, Benchmark Start/Stop events and Profile Enter/Exit events. Events must be enabled and/or instrumented on target application to be visible. 
		Concurrency.Tip=Select this feature to analyze how efficiently the application is utilizing multi-core. RTOS context switch events must be enabled on all required cores for this analysis.
		ContextAwareProfile.Tip=Select this feature to get Function inclusive and exclusive time based on Profile Enter/Exit events instrumentation. Enable RTOS Context Switch events to get context aware profiling.
		Duration.Tip=Select this feature to analyze Benchmark Start/Stop events.
		TaskProfiler.Tip=Select this feature analyze the time tasks are spending in different states. RTOS Context Switch events must be enabled.
		CPULoad.Tip=Select this feature to see CPU load graph and load summary statistics. RTOS load logging must be enabled.
		TaskLoad.Tip=Select this feature to see the loading of each task, HWI and/or SWIs are putting on the CPU. The corresponding RTOS load logging must be enabled.
		CountAnalysis.Tip=Select this feature to get statistics of any value logged in the application.
		PrintfLogs.Tip=Select this feature to open the Printf log view showing Error, Warning, Info and Print Events

	</dvt.property>
</project>

